{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Android?",
      "options": ["Operating System", "Frame Work", "Library", "Application"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is activity in android",
      "options": ["Backend code", "User interface", "Networking", "Library"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is adapter in android?",
      "options": [
        "Child View",
        "Storage class",
        "Binds the parent to child view",
        "Child View to represent parent view items"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is shared preferences in android?",
      "options": [
        "Store the data in android",
        "Store the data in cloud",
        "Transfer the from android to cloud",
        "Transfer the from cloud to android"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the importance of setting permissions in app development?",
      "options": [
        "Protect data",
        "Protect code",
        "Protect data and code",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What Storages are available in android",
      "options": [
        "Internal storage",
        "External storage",
        "SQLite database",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is modern language for developing android app?",
      "options": ["Java", "Javascript", "Kotlin", "Flutter"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Retrofit in Android?",
      "options": [
        "REST api Library",
        "Api fetching frame work",
        "Networking library",
        "Image processing library"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How to find view element into the program?",
      "options": [
        "findViewByElement",
        "findViewById",
        "findViewByClass",
        "findView"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ADB stands for?",
      "options": [
        "Application Developement Board",
        "Application Deployment Branch",
        "Android Developement Bridge",
        "Android Debugging Bridge"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is defined as a lightweight thread?",
      "options": [
        "MVVM architecture",
        "Coroutines",
        "Global Scope",
        "Thread pooling"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What does android serializable do?",
      "options": [
        "Passes view between activies",
        "Passes api request between activites",
        "Passes fragment between activities",
        "Passes data between activities"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    }
  ]
}
